Slick VPNs Privacy Policy explained in detail       

==========================================================================================================================================

Toggle navigation

Save Now!

Up to 60% Off!

* Blazing Fast Speeds
    
* Anonymous Traffic
    
* Unlimited Bandwidth
    
* Unlimited Web Traffic
    
* Servers in over 85 cities
    
* Bitcoin Accepted
    
* Privacy Protection
    
* 30 day Money Back Guarantee

SlickVPN’s Privacy Policy
-------------------------

### **The Information We Collect**

SlickVPN does not ask for any personally identifiable information to browse our site or use our free features. To subscribe to our services, an account must be registered. We do not use this information to track any of your web activities while logged into our SlickVPN services. We only collect the necessary and limited information for our customer information file in order to provide and maintain billing for our services.

To maximize your privacy, SlickVPN only collects the minimum information required to create your account.

*  eMail
* Username/Password
* Apache Webserver Data
* Payment Data necessary to manage subscriptions, payments, and cancellations
* Any emails sent to our service
* Google analytics data to help market our product
* Temporary cookies to manage members area login

SlickVPN collects certain information automatically from visitors to the site which includes the IP address and which pages are viewed on the site. For more information on this process, please see the Cookies and Tracking section below. **However, user activities outside of the SlickVPN site are not tracked nor do we track the browsing activities of user who are logged to the SlickVPN service.**

### **Situations When SlickVPN May Disclose Your Information To Others**

SlickVPN does not sell or rent any personal information of our subscribers to others. In compliance with local laws and under the following circumstances, we may disclose personal information of you to third parties for the following reasons:

* **Service Providers** – With third party service provides who may provide services on our behalf such as payment processors, hosting platforms for SlickVPN and sending email messages for the company. Our service providers will only receive the information they absolutely need in order to perform the designated functions of each. None are permitted to use or disclose this information for their own marketing or for any other purposes.
* **Business Transfers** – To any acquiring company if, at any point, we are acquired or merged with another company.
* **Legal** – In accordance with local law, a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal processes that we are legally obligated
* **Internal SlickVPN Policies** – In order to prevent, investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or situations involving potential threats that violate our Terms or this Policy.

### **Marketing Emails**

From time to time, SlickVPN may send you information regarding our promotions and/or information regarding our products and services that you may be interested in. You may unsubscribe from these emails at any time by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.slickvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject title “Please unsubscribe me”. In addition, the emails you receive will always contain an unsubscribe link that you may also use to opt out of receiving future emails from us. However, we may still send you important emails that may pertain to your account or any other customer service related issues.  
**How SlickVPN May Use Your Information**

The only information that is collected through the SlickVPN site and services are primarily used to create new accounts, collect payments for the services and identify and communicate with current subscribers. We also use this information to help and communicate with current subscribers to offer troubleshooting procedures for our customer support department.

SlickVPN may also periodically use personal information collected for the following reasons”

* Internal record keeping
* To complete an online order
* Administer and improve the SlickVPN site and services
* Verify your identity when you login to the SlickVPN site or services
* To respond to your requests or inquiries for customer service purposes

Analyze usage and trends via our Analytics data to better understand how users use our website and services

### **How To Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or would like further information on our privacy practices, we encourage you to email us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.slickvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### **International Users**

The systems used at SlickVPN are based out of the United States, so your personal information will only be processed by us in the US, where data protection and privacy regulations may differ than in other countries. Once an online account is created with SlickVPN from outside of US, you agree to the terms of this Policy, Terms of Service and grant us consent to transfer and process your information to the United States. Which may or may not offer an equal level of data protection of other countries, dependent on the country of origin.

### **Our Security Standards**

At SlickVPN, we use a variety of security measures that either meet or excel industry standards to protect your personal information from either theft, loss, misuse or unauthorized access or disclosure or destruction.

Where appropriate, we use encryption, access controls, passwords, and/or physical security measures to protect the personal information we collect and maintain about you against unauthorized access and disclosure. Despite our efforts, no data security methods guarantee 100% protection. We do not, nor should any company promise or guarantee that your personal information can never be viewed and/or used by others.

### **Cookies**

We do not track user activities outside of the SlickVPN website or of users when they are logged into our VPN Services.

We may use or engage others to use cookies, clear gifs, and similar technologies to understand how users access and use our Site. In general, you can browse our Site without telling us who you are or submitting any personal information. However, we collect the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site, as well as other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our Site. We use this information to help us understand Site activity and to monitor and improve our Site.

_Cookies_. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent-based cookies. Session cookies exist only during an online session; we use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you while you are logged in to your account at the Site. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity.

_Disabling Cookies_. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Site visitors who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Site but certain Site features will not function.

_Clear GIFs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_. We or the third parties we engage may employ clear GIFs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) to help us better manage content on the Site by among other things, tracking the activities of our Site visitors and compiling statistics about Site usage. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages or within emails.

_Third Parties_. We may engage third parties, such as Google Analytics, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable Site data. These third parties may use cookies and clear GIFs on our Site to collect, analyze, and generate reports on Site usage for us. We do not provide these third parties with any personal information that we have collected about you.

### **Children’s Privacy**

The website and services of SlickVPN are not intended for anyone under the age of 18. If you are either a parent or guardian and believe that your underage child has provided personal information to us, please contact us immediately at [\[email protected\]](https://www.slickvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) so that we can delete the child’s information.

### **How To Modify Your Personal Information**

You may review or edit your account information at any time from the member login section of the SlickVPN website. However, if there are any other changes that you wish to make that are not listed in the members area should be sent to [\[email protected\]](https://www.slickvpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) We will respond to all requests in a timely manner.

### **Links To Other Sites**

As a convenience to our users, we provide links to our websites to third parties. These links are neither an endorsement nor a referral to the linked websites. We suggest that you carefully read the privacy statements, notices and terms of services of any other websites that you also visit. As we do not have any control over these websites, we therefore assume no responsibility for the manner in which organizations operate to collect, use maintain or disclose personal information.

### **Changes to this Policy**

SlickVPN reserves the right to change the details of this privacy policy at any time. In such cases, SlickVPN will take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes re brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our website. Before any changes to the new policy becomes effective, we will also email our existing customers.

#### VPN Links

Search

Search

#### Information

#### Contact Information

**SLICKVPN**  
Weston Road PMB #231  
Weston, Florida 33331, USA  

#### VPN Packages

[Monthly

* Special Price:
* 10.00

* Regular Price:
* $10](https://www.slickvpn.com/l52/checkout/order) [Yearly

* Special Price:
* 48.00

* Regular Price:
* $120](https://www.slickvpn.com/l52/checkout/order) [6 Months

* Special Price:
* 30.00

* Regular Price:
* $60](https://www.slickvpn.com/l52/checkout/order) 

© SlickVPN2024. All Rights Reserved.
